* How Klarna works
    
* Help

* How Klarna works
    
* Help

Shopping categories

How Klarna works

Help

* Customer login

* Business login

    Log in to manage your orders, payout reports, store statistics, and general settings.

Log in

Secure and private. By design.
==============================

We understand the importance of keeping your personal and financial information secure and private. From making sure you get what you pay for, to fraud monitoring and data encryption, we’re here to make sure you can always shop and pay with peace of mind.

Your data, your call
--------------------

We are private by design. You own and control the data that you share with us and security is built directly into our products. We are fully committed to protecting and handling your data in a transparent and secure way. 

Built-in privacy

Your privacy comes first, our products are designed and built to safeguard your data while still being easy to use.

Always in control

You can easily manage, review, or delete your personal data through our App, website, or Customer Service.

Open and transparent

The reasons we collect and process your data are easily accessible and clearly outlined in our Privacy Policy.

Enhanced data protection

We only collect the information we need to give you the best experience possible and we use data encryption to keep it safe.

Our privacy terms
-----------------

How we process and safeguard your data

Our Privacy Policy provides all the information about how we use your personal data and outlines our commitment to protect your personal data.

How we provide the best shopping experience

The Klarna Shopping Service terms explain how we provide an optimal shopping experience, including explaining details regarding your account, our payment methods, and how we protect your purchases.

How we use tracking technologies

Our Privacy Policy details how we use tracking technologies to optimize the functionality of our website and improve your user experience. It also explains how you can control the use of these tracking technologies.

Privacy FAQs
------------

How does Klarna collect my data?

When you use Klarna, there are two ways we can receive your personal data: 

1. Personal data that you provide to us. This includes, for example, your contact- and identification information or your payment information.
    
2. Personal data that we collect about you from a variety of sources. We receive information from credit and fraud prevention agencies, stores, or public databases, among others. This can include name, date of birth, place of birth, financial information, or how you use our service. 

Which purposes does Klarna use my data for?

As we continuously work to elevate your shopping experience, we may use your data for a variety of reasons, for example: 

* Verify your identity when you use our services or contact us
    
* Engage with you as a customer
    
* Provide you with the services you requested
    
* Give you an overview on your financial situation
    
* Understand your eligibility for Klarna products and services
    
* Communicate information on the products we offer
    
* Conduct customer satisfaction survey
    
* Carry out credit and fraud assessments
    
* Perform debt collection service
    
* Prevent IT attack
    
* Meet regulatory and legal requirements

For more detailed information about the different reasons for collecting and using each type of your data, see our

.

How does Klarna use my data?

We value and respect your data, and always seek to improve your everyday interactions with us. Here are key ways your personal data, once shared with us, serves to benefit you:

* **Paying with Klarna:** We perform internal and third-party credit checks, gather contact and ID information, and analyze interactions with Klarna to understand your eligibility for our products and services.
    
* **Autofill:** We offer the option to save your contact, ID, and payment details for faster transactions. You can always opt-out in 'autofill settings' during checkout or via a form.
    
* **Klarna App:** We collect data on app interactions, past purchases, linked bank transactions, and preferred items to enhance the app experience and provide personalized offerings like tracking deliveries, price drop notifications, and financial overview.
    
* **Support:** We gather contact and ID details and document past conversations to ensure efficient, personalized support and faster response times.
    
* **Safe shopping:** We record contact and ID information, financial details, device data, and interaction information to protect against fraud and money laundering. 
    
* **Communication and Offers:** We keep records of prior purchases, interactions, and device details to send updates, offers, and product recommendations.

For more detailed information on how we process your data, see our

.

How is the security of my information ensured?

Your information security and privacy is the most important to us at Klarna. These are some of the measures we take in our approach to protect your data:

* **Investment in State-of-the-art Systems:** Our advanced security infrastructure vigilantly monitors our ecosystem, identifying any suspicious activity.
    
* **Proactive Risk Management:** Before developing our products, we conduct rigorous risk assessments and implement preventive measures to maintain robust security.
    
* **Data Encryption:** We utilize appropriate encryption techniques to protect your data from unauthorized access.
    
* **Limited Access within the organization:** We ensure that only authorized individuals have access to your data.
    
* **Compliance with Regulations:** As a finance institution, we are subject to regular external audits which scrutinize our security protocols to maintain the highest standards.

How can I control the use of my data?

There are a number of ways you can control the data we collect as well as the way we use it.

* **Autofill:** Within the Klarna App you can choose to opt out of the Autofill feature which automatically fills in relevant information when you make future purchases. You can choose to opt out of this feature in the ‘Autofill settings’ during address registration in your purchase checkout or reviewing our support section below.
    
* **Marketing communication:** In order to unsubscribe from marketing send-outs you can easily click on the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of each email. You can also opt out through the settings in the Klarna App under ‘Communication preferences’, or reach out to us via email stating your wish to opt out from marketing send-outs.
    
* **Identification:** You can personalize how you would like us to verify your identity before each purchase within the Klarna App. Simply go to the Klarna App and choose “Settings”/”Privacy & Security”

For more detailed information on how to control your data, see our

.

How can I review and access my data?

You can review and access a copy of all personal data that we store about you at any time. Simply fill in the request form below, and make sure to provide all email addresses that you have used with Klarna before. In order to complete your request, we need you to provide your complete and correct information to verify your identity.

Our Customer Service will handle your request and send you an encrypted PDF file via email. This file can include information connected to, for example, previous purchases you have made with Klarna and our products and services you have used.

How can I delete my data?

You have the right to request deletion of your personal data. When you exercise your right to be forgotten, your data will be deleted and all agreements you have with us will be terminated. As a bank, we are required by law to retain certain personal data even after your deletion request. We may also retain certain information based on legitimate interest to protect you and us, e.g. for fraud prevention purposes.

Once you have exercised your right to be forgotten, you will no longer be able to access previous orders or your account. You can place new orders again after we have successfully deleted your data.

To request data deletion, simply fill in the request form below, and make sure to provide all email addresses that you have used with Klarna before. In order to handle your request, we need you to provide your complete and correct information to verify your identity.

Does Klarna share my data?

Depending on the service you wish to use, we may need to share some of your data with a select number of third parties, for example partners (cloud computing platforms, payment service providers or advertising or marketing partners) or authorities. To give you some examples, the reason for this may be so we can store your data safely, administer your purchases with stores, abide by regulatory requirements, prevent fraud, carry out credit risk assessments, or conduct marketing or advertising.

You may opt out of certain types of sharing under GLBA; to limit our sharing of non-public personal information with unaffiliated third parties under Gramm-Leech-Bliley Act simply go to the Klarna app: sign in to the Klarna App, go to Settings, then “Privacy” to adjust your settings. If you don’t have the Klarna App, you can go to the WebApp at app.klarna.com, then log-in, click ‘’Settings’’, then “Privacy” to adjust your settings.

For more information, please read our

. If you are a California Resident, you can learn more on our

.

Send us your privacy request
----------------------------

You’re in control. Choose an option from the form below and make sure to provide complete and correct data, including all email addresses you have used with Klarna.

1\. Delete your personal data

If you exercise your right to be forgotten, we will delete your personal data and terminate your customer relationship with us. You will no longer be able to access previous orders or your account, but you can place new orders again after we have deleted your data. Due to legal requirements or legitimate interest, we may retain certain personal data even after your deletion request is completed. 

2\. Correct your personal data

You can have inaccurate data corrected for your name, date of birth and billing address.

Please go to the [Your California privacy choices page](https://www.klarna.com/us/your-california-privacy-choices/) if you are a California resident.

Please choose one of the following request types.

Correct my personal dataDelete my personal dataMy Privacy Request

**Delete my personal data**

By requesting your data to be deleted you terminate all agreements you have with us.

All fields marked with an \* are required.

**Correct my personal data**

All fields marked with an \* are required.

First name \*

Last name \*

Email used to place orders \*

Please confirm your email \*

Additional email address used to place orders (optional)

Additional email address used to place orders (optional)

Additional email address used to place orders (optional)

Date of birth \*

For more information about how we handle your personal data, please read our

.

**Please select which of the below details you wish to have rectified:**

Name

Date of birth

Billing address

**Please upload one of the following documents in order to verify these changes:**

For name and/or date of birth - Passport, Driving licence, Birth certificate, Marriage certificate or Death certificate.

For billing address - Utility Bill, Bank statements, Government issued letter (must be dated within the last 90 days).

Upload files here

Please note that this form serves to rectify your name, DOB or billing address. To change any other type of personal data such as email address, phone number, etc. please reach out to our service center.

For your security, please feel free to redact any information not applicable before attaching.

For more information about how we handle your personal data, please read our

.

Safety comes standard
---------------------

When we say we’re there for you, we mean it.

With every click, we make sure your data and information is protected. That means every time you open the app, we make sure it’s really you and each time you make a payment, we encrypt your personal information, making sure it stays between us.

Pay it safe

Fraud detection is at the heart of Klarna's security. We can quickly respond to unusual activity on your account, and if needed, we will ask for an extra security step called a multi-factor authentication (MFA), which will ensure that it’s really you making a purchase and giving you peace of mind that your financial information is safe.

Shop securely with buyer protection

If you shop with Klarna and run into issues, like your order doesn't arrive or it's not what you expected, we've got your back. Just give the store a chance to sort it out first, and if that doesn't help, we'll step in to help you get a refund and even pause your payments in case of returns.

You’re in the driver’s seat

When it comes to your data, it isn’t just a question of keeping it safe, it’s about making it easy for you to be in control of your information. We’ll also send you a notification whenever you make a change to your account and an alert with every new login into you account.

Security tips
-------------

Shopping should be fun, but it's important to be aware of potential risks to help you stay safe. That's where our security tips come into play.

We want to prevent scams and unauthorized activity from happening in the first place. These tips are straightforward and easy to apply, so don’t wait - dive into our tips to stay in the loop.

Top 4 ways to spot a scammer
----------------------------

We’ve narrowed down a few of the top ways to spot a scammer. When something doesn’t seem right - your intuition may be picking up on subtle scam signals.

1\. Unexpected messages

Scammers often initiate contact through unsolicited emails, phone calls, or text messages and extract sensitive information.

2\. Time crunch

Scammers often create a false sense of urgency to pressure you into acting quickly without thinking.

3\. The more you know

Before shopping or sharing personal details online, make sure the website is legit and secure.

4\. Too good to be true

Scammers may ask you to pay using gift cards, the Klarna app, or even a wire transfer with the expectation you’ll receive even more in return.

What should I do if I...?
-------------------------

I receive a suspicious email/text message?

Do not click any links or open attachments from unexpected or unverified sources. Always be cautious of communication requesting personal or financial information, demanding immediate action, or simply does not look right. If possible, flag the message as spam or junk. Your awareness and vigilance are the best lines of defense. 

I shared my personal identification or authentication code to someone I don’t know?

Immediately contact Klarna and any other relevant institutions involved to notify them about the incident. Swift action could trigger preventative measures that can avert further complications. Change all relevant passwords and monitor your financial statements closely for any signs of unauthorized activity.

I have lost my device or physical card?

Immediately contact Klarna to report the lost device or card. Freeze your card to prevent unauthorized charges. Similarly, if a device like a phone or laptop is lost, change all passwords for accounts accessible on the device and inform relevant institutions about possible unauthorized access - especially if the device is auto-logged into any financial or personal accounts. 

I see unauthorized activity on my account?

Immediately contact Klarna to report the suspicious activity. Consider changing any log-in credentials you believe could be compromised and enable additional security measures like two-factor authentication. Regularly monitoring your account for unfamiliar activity can help detect potential fraud early.

I am asked to make an urgent payment?

Always double-check before conducting any transactions, particularly those demanding urgently and unexpectedly. Contact the requester via a different, trusted method to confirm its legitimacy.

I suspect an online shopping site could be fraudulent?

Before sharing information online, research the company, check reviews, and confirm valid contact information. 

Make sure the website is legit and secure. Double check the website’s URL is spelled correctly. Also, look for "https://" in the URL which means the data you send to the site is encrypted, providing an extra layer of security. Especially when using public Wi-Fi networks. If something feels off, trust your instincts.

I clicked an unknown link and it downloaded a file?

Do not open the file. Delete it immediately and run a virus scan. Ensure you have up-to-date antivirus software installed to protect against malicious downloads. Continue to monitor your financial statements closely for any unauthorized activity.

I am contacted by someone claiming they're from a well-known company?

Always proceed with caution when contacted unexpectedly, even if they appear to be legitimate from a place you trust. If in doubt, end the conversation and independently contact the company directly using a verified method such as the customer service number listed on their official website. It’s always better to double-check before sharing any personal or financial information.

Need help?
----------

We're always ready to support you with any security or privacy questions.

Klarna

Customer

Business

United States

Choose your language and region

Klarna is available around the world with a variable offering, choose one that suits you best.

[United States

English](https://www.klarna.com/us/)

[Australia

English](https://www.klarna.com/au/)

[Österreich

Deutsch](https://www.klarna.com/at/)

[België

Nederlands](https://www.klarna.com/be/)

[Belgique

Français](https://www.klarna.com/be/fr/)

[Canada

English](https://www.klarna.com/ca/)

[Canada

Français](https://www.klarna.com/ca/fr/)

[中国

中文(简体](https://www.klarna.com/cn/)

[Česká republika

Čeština](https://www.klarna.com/cz/)

[Danmark

Dansk](https://www.klarna.com/dk/)

[Suomi

Suomi](https://www.klarna.com/fi/)

[France

Français](https://www.klarna.com/fr/)

[Deutschland

Deutsch](https://www.klarna.com/de/)

[Ελλάδα

Ελληνικά](https://www.klarna.com/gr/)

[Magyarország

Magyar](https://www.klarna.com/hu/)

[Ireland

English](https://www.klarna.com/ie/)

[Italia

Italiano](https://www.klarna.com/it/)

[日本

日本語](https://www.klarna.com/jp/)

[México

Español](https://www.klarna.com/mx/)

[Nederland

Nederlands](https://www.klarna.com/nl/)

[New Zealand

English](https://www.klarna.com/nz/)

[Norge

Norsk](https://www.klarna.com/no/)

[Polska

Polski](https://www.klarna.com/pl/)

[Portugal

Português](https://www.klarna.com/pt/)

[España

Español](https://www.klarna.com/es/)

[Slovensko

Slovenčin](https://www.klarna.com/sk/)

[Sverige

Svenska](https://www.klarna.com/se/)

[Schweiz

Deutsch](https://www.klarna.com/ch/)

[Switzerland

English](https://www.klarna.com/ch/en/)

[Suisse

Français](https://www.klarna.com/ch/fr/)

[Svizzera

Italiano](https://www.klarna.com/ch/it/)

[United Kingdom

English](https://www.klarna.com/uk/)

[România

Română](https://www.klarna.com/ro/)

Monthly financing through Klarna and One-time card bi-weekly payments with a service fee to shop anywhere in the Klarna App issued by WebBank. Other CA resident loans at select merchants made or arranged pursuant to a California Financing Law license. Copyright © 2005-2024 Klarna Inc. NMLS #1353190, 800 N. High Street Columbus, OH 43215. VT Consumers: For WebBank Loan Products (One-Time Cards, Financing, Klarna Card): THIS IS A LOAN SOLICITATION ONLY. KLARNA INC. IS NOT THE LENDER. INFORMATION RECEIVED WILL BE SHARED WITH ONE OR MORE THIRD PARTIES IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR LOAN INQUIRY. THE LENDER MAY NOT BE SUBJECT TO ALL VERMONT LENDING LAWS. THE LENDER MAY BE SUBJECT TO FEDERAL LENDING LAWS.
